{
    "subject": "resource/Mohammed_Nasif_Kheirbek",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek (Arabic: \u0645\u062d\u0645\u062f \u0646\u0627\u0635\u064a\u0641 \u062e\u064a\u0631\u0628\u0643\u200e) known as Mohammed Nasif or Abu Wael, (10 April 1937 - 28 June 2015) was the deputy vice-president for security affairs in Syria. He was a close adviser of Syrian President Bashar Assad and is Syria's point-man for its relationship with Iran and Lebanon's Shia militias. He is one of a number of officials sanctioned by the European Union for the use of violence against protesters participating in the Syrian civil war.",
    "human_readable": "Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek's abstract is Mohammed Nasif or Abu Wael, (10 April 1937 - 28 June 2015) was the deputy vice-president for security affairs in Syria, a close adviser of Syrian President Bashar Assad and is Syria's point-man for its relationship with Iran and Lebanon's Shia militias. He is one of a number of officials sanctioned by the European Union for the use of violence against protesters participating in the Syrian civil war.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9499272704124451,
            "question": "Who was Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek a close advisor to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9324951767921448,
            "question": "What is the significance of Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek's relationship with Iran and Lebanon's Shia militias?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9195111989974976,
            "question": "Which countries did Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek act as Syria's point-man for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.896703839302063,
            "question": "What was Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek's role in the Syrian government?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8529587388038635,
            "question": "When was Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.849975049495697,
            "question": "What was Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek's other known name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8310393691062927,
            "question": "What type of violence was Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek accused of using against protesters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8267126679420471,
            "question": "When did Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7954527735710144,
            "question": "What reason led to the European Union sanctioning Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5044946074485779,
            "question": "What was the Syrian civil war about?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek's abstract is Mohammed Nasif or Abu Wael, (10 April 1937 - 28 June 2015) was the deputy vice-president for security affairs in Syria, a close adviser of Syrian President Bashar Assad and is Syria's point-man for its relationship with Iran and Lebanon's Shia militias. He is one of a number of officials sanctioned by the European Union for the use of violence against protesters participating in the Syrian civil war.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5142_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What reason led to the European Union sanctioning Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5142_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek pass away?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5142_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of violence was Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek accused of using against protesters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5142_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5142_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5142_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5142_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5142_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5142_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5142_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5142_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5142_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5142_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5142_53.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I will evaluate whether the triple \"Muhammad Nasif Kheir Bek (a.k.a. Mohammad Nassif Kheir Bek) was a security adviser to President Bashar al-Assad\" is supported by the documents.\n\nHere's the evaluation:\n\n- The document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5142/re-ranker-msmarco/23.txt mentions that Samir Joumaa\u2019s closeness to President Bashar al-Assad and Mohammed Nassif Kheir Bek means that he is implicated in the policy of repression conducted by the Syrian regime against its opponents.\n- The document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5142/re-ranker-msmarco/32.txt mentions \"For almost 20 years he has been head of the office of Mohammad Nassif Kheir Bek, one of the main security advisers of Bashar al-Assad (and officially deputy to the Vice-President, Farouk al-Sharaa)\".\n- The document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5142/re-ranker-msmarco/20.txt lists KHAYRBIK, Muhammad Nasif as Syrian Deputy Vice President for Security Affairs.\n\nAll the documents support the statement that Mohammad Nassif Kheir Bek was a security adviser to President Bashar al-Assad. Therefore, the answer is:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe provided context information supports the abstract about Mohammed Nasif Kheir Bek. The documents mention that he was:\n\n- A deputy vice-president for security affairs in Syria.\n- One of the main security advisers of Syrian President Bashar al-Assad.\n- Officially a deputy to the Vice-President, Farouk al-Sharaa.\n\nThese details align with the provided abstract. Additionally, while the specific dates (10 April 1937 - 28 June 2015) are not mentioned in the given context, they can be inferred as part of the broader information about his role and lifespan. The mention of sanctions by OFAC also supports the abstract's reference to him being sanctioned for violence against protesters during the Syrian civil war.\n\nTherefore, based on this information, the answer is \"yes.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}